Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
To be continued...
Come on, sister! Stay with us!
Old Hag, wake up! You can't die on me!
If you keeled over now, Marie would be sad.
And I... wouldn't be too happy about it either.
Take... take care of them.
The children...
It's always the same.
No matter who wins on any battlefield, it's the weak who pay the greatest price.
Children are innocent, untouched by sin.
They were the ones I most wanted to protect.
And so I left the battlefield behind, and devoted myself to the church.
Sister!
What kind of nonsense is that?
No one is pure. You're all tainted by sin from the moment of your birth.
You're insane!
Just look at you, Sally. Poor thing. They've hurt you so badly.
I tried, Master.
You did well, but now it's time for you to rest.
Valtos...
Yes, sir.
To be continued...
That's a deal.
Bye, Asta. Catch you later.
Don't forget, Precious.
You belong to me.
Please just leave me alone!
i'm to blame for this i should never have sent her here by herself this outcome was unexpected
you needn't feel responsible for what happened we all know how they fight
no doubt they resorted to underhanded tactics you're saying that we fight dirty after what
that crazy lackey of yours did to those poor kids you know the sister was wrong before
it isn't the weak who pay not at all it is the strong who have been victimized
feared discriminated against persecuted and stolen from what's he talking about that's crazy
for its crimes the clover kingdom cannot be forgiven instead we will destroy you as you so richly
deserve and build a nation of our own where do you get off acting like we're the bad guys here
you and your group of psychos started all this you jerk
i refuse to listen to that kind of filth it's painful really seeing someone as disgusting as you
with that grimoire my grimoire never mind i need to stay focused on his attacks
they come so fast i can't even see them what do i do
the only thing i can do use my sword as a shield to block any fatal blows
i'm not dying yes you are i'll just be taking that grimoire back from you now
this is it
i'm dead
no way
captain yummy what are you doing here
why am i here well hell kid i guess i must have gotten lost anybody know where the bar is
what are you doing here
oh
in
What's your face for you?
水平線が中央魔王
何度挫かれても
その希望を両手に
僕ら波を打って
ツバッシャーを
シーセローと叫ぶんだ
Get down!
We all let you down!
Best one!
Can you bring me down?
Back up!
Get far out of the sky!
Black Clover!
いつか共に
火を今は黒に染めよう
こんなふざけた時代
Black Clover!
今日の間に
僕ら並べたって
今から
扉を
開くから
Let's go!
これが
Got rocks in there instead of brains?
That's what people call a joke.
What?
I'm a magic knight and there's trouble.
That's what I'm doing here, idiot.
We heard about what was going on,
but everyone back at the hideout was useless as usual,
so here I am.
I'll kill them all later.
They couldn't pull it together this once?!
This is why we're here?
I wish he'd just let me sleep.
What the hell are you doing anyway?
I gave all you knuckleheads the day off.
Maybe what you need is a more permanent vacation.
So, what's up with this guy?
He says he's the leader of the Hive and Midnight Sun.
No way! Not them again!
Oh yeah?
Here I've been picturing a super buff guy
who ate cows whole or something.
Not some scrawny freak.
Not everything in this world is about muscles.
This guy has magic power practically pouring out of him.
It's bottomless.
And light magic?
That's super rare stuff.
Only a few people in the whole history of the Clover Kingdom have ever wielded it.
Whatever happens next, it isn't going to be pretty.
I want to go home.
So, the Black Bull's captain came himself.
Shall I summon the Third Eye now?
No need.
You see, the captain here is a wielder of dark magic.
I'll enjoy pitting my power against his in battle.
Hey, Finral.
Can you get the others to the village?
Sure, leave it to me.
But what about you?
I can still fight!
This is my chance to see Captain Yami in action.
No way am I leaving now!
Gosh, and...
Well, whoever you are, can you walk?
Shooter the old hag first!
And hurry!
Right, got it!
Never mind that I'm actually your superior.
Alright, Captain.
It's up to you now.
Hey, you better be coming back.
Did he know I was planning to sneak off?
He couldn't, right?
Well, you know, I think I might be a little low on Mana.
So, really, I'm not kidding!
Yeah?
Look at my face.
Does it look like I'm kidding?
No, sir.
I guess it doesn't.
Are you trying to mess up my ride or something?
His ride?
All right, time to get out of here.
I'm not looking to die today.
I'm off!
Gotta get these people to safety!
You better be coming back, you hear me, Finral?
So cool!
How'd you know that strike was coming?
What kind of sword is that?
Where'd you get him?
Shut up, would ya?
This is a katana.
It's from my native country, the Land of the Sun.
I blocked his hit by...
Oh, never mind.
No time to explain.
Besides, it's boring that way.
Just watch.
Engage light magic.
Light swords of conviction.
Awesome!
He's using reinforcement magic to boost his natural abilities and cloaking his sword in dark magic to slice through my spell.
Except, there's more to it than that.
Very well.
Let's try something else, then.
Impressive.
The power of an unorthodox grand magic knight.
Hold on.
You know?
I think I recognize you from somewhere.
Except I'm pretty sure I'd remember if I knew somebody who could use light magic.
So who are you and what's your angle?
Do you go around attacking people just for kicks?
My angle, let me tell you a story.
Once upon a time, in a certain village, there lived people who had tremendous magic power.
They were special, greatly loved by the mana of this world.
They could control weather at will and manipulate the minerals.
Their powers were truly godlike.
Indeed, those outside their village came to revere them as divine beings.
But then, the people's feelings began to change.
Their respect and admiration became fear and envy.
They slaughtered their gods in a cowardly surprise attack and stole their power.
What kind of story is that?
Who cares?
You planning to become a bard?
Well, I've got a story of my own you might like to hear.
It was once a young man with a bright mind and a pure heart.
His father was a fisherman who sent him out to work the sea at a young age.
Then one day, his boat got wrecked.
Seriously?
He fell into the water and washed up on an unknown shore.
Who is this kid?
He's very impressive.
He looked and acted different than the people there, so we got the crap beat out of him a lot.
But that was okay.
Because he turned around to beat the crap out of them and then became a badass squad boss.
The end.
Well, I think it's a pretty good story.
Of course, it is half my life, so there's that.
Silence!
How dare you, Mark Master Licht!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
That is one seriously freaky face!
What are those weird-looking lines for?
Now's not really the time!
He's gotten faster.
If you're truly a foreigner, then my tale has nothing to do with you.
In which case, feel free to leave.
Captain Yami!
You've avoided mortal blows, but how much longer will your luck hold?
Are you the guy who messed up Wigolion so bad, huh?
That's right.
I prepared so very carefully, and he walked right into my trap.
Figured as much.
These little darts wouldn't do anything to a guy like him.
He'd take you down.
You've done that.
I'll just cover it in a distance.
Game by moderates of Wigolion.
Let's do something.
We'll see.
This little monsters have for us.
Oh, no.
Wigolion.
Let's do something.
Hakes!
What?
Now dark magic, dark cloaks.
Lightless Slash!
Master Litt!
That was amazing! I've never seen anything like it before!
Of course you used a trap. You couldn't win unless you played dirty.
Who are you?
Stop dancing around and come at me head on.
I'll show you what a squad captain can do. Think you can handle it?
Master Litt!
Hey kid, were you watching?
Uh, yes sir!
That's good, because now it's your turn.
Yes sir!
Wait, what did you say? There's no way I can do that!
Yeah? Last I checked, I was still your captain.
Which means if I tell you to do something, you do it. Assuming you want to be a real man someday, Shrimpster.
Please sir, that really hurts!
He blocked Master Litt's attacks, and even managed to fight back.
The captain of the Black Bulls. Could his power possibly rival the Wizard King's?
Hmph. Fascinating. The power of dark magic.
Now, light recovery magic. Healing light particles.
Come on! Really? He can use recovery magic too?
I haven't seen it much myself.
But apparently, some people who've got a lot of mana can wield all kinds of different magic.
It's especially rare for attack types like him to be able to heal too.
Never mind that for now. You ready to go?
He was serious?!
Please sir, this is impossible! I can't do what you just did!
You remember I can't use magic, right?
I'm not talking about that last attack, moron.
I'm in this move here where I block his stupid little lightning bolts, see?
How do I hit something if I don't even know it's there?
Guess I've got no choice. I'll explain it to you once. For 500 Yule.
He's charging me?!
You wanna know how I've been able to respond to his attacks?
It's cause I've been picking up on something that the people back in my country call Ki.
Ki? You weren't sensing his mana?
Nope.
A person's glance. Their breathing. Their scent.
The way their muscles move. The hint of their presence.
Taken together. All of that living energy people give off. That's called Ki.
All I've been doing is reading his Ki and using it to predict his moves.
You've never done anything like that before?
Actually, yeah.
That's my fighting style. I combine the ability to sense Ki with my magic and the strength of my muscles.
Think of it as me being a buff magical swordsman.
You're not kidding about the buff part. Your neck's as thick as a tree.
Huh. Have you seen your neck lately?
Insolent. Carrying on a conversation mid-battle. Do they think we're fools?
That captain certainly is a mystery. He's surprisingly quick for someone who looks so sloppy.
He cannot be permitted to show you any further disrespect, Master. Please pardon my impertinence, but if I may step in...
Much appreciated, Valtos. You're always so eager to be of use. All right. The boy, perhaps.
Would you capture him for me? I don't mind if you need to hurt him a bit.
What? It would be my pleasure, Master.
That was close!
Hey, good timing. Practice on the evil scarecrow over there.
What? You want me to take on that guy? We talked about this! There's no way I'll be able to...
There's a saying where I'm from. Whatever happens, a warrior never goes back on his word.
You did say you were going to be the Wizard King, right?
This is where you've got to push past your limits. If you don't, then your path ends here.
Yes, sir!
I have no idea what I'm supposed to do. So I'll just concentrate. Concentrate.
You truly think you'll be able to detect my attacks? An idiot boy who can use magic.
There it is!
I guess I missed some.
Nice try. You think I wouldn't notice you using just one of your senses? The only things you had work in there were your ears.
That isn't reading, Ki. If you want to do this right, then you've got to feel it with your whole body. You got that?
My whole body?
Yep. Don't rely only on your ears or just your eyes. It's like, uh, something in between intuition and prediction. Now do it right this time or I'll kill you.
This is insane!
Still, I think I kind of get it now. Not only my ears, not just my eyes. All right. I gotta reset everything. And concentrate.
Yes! There it is!
It worked!
Captain Yummy, did you see me?
Really? You actually managed to pull it off? No way. You're a freak.
What?
Valtos.
You hurt him.
How dare you?
I will not allow humans like you to continue harming my compatriots.
You've done too much damage already.
Jeez. What's this guy's problem? They're the ones who started all this?
Yeah.
As you can see, this particular spell traces an ever-changing track of whip-like undulations.
Can you anticipate these movements?
Long ago, when a person had sinned, the punishment was flogging.
One popular instrument used was a whip.
I find this a very fitting in for the likes of you.
Light creation magic.
Light whip of judgment.
Your struggles are pointless.
It's crumbling!
That nutball's not holding anything back!
Aaaaaaah!
Aaaaah!
Goodness! And here I was attempting to restrain myself!
Poor fools! You truly are weak!
Your kingdom as well. It too will fall.
You destroyed them, Master!
Surely only a god could wield such power!
If you wished it, all of the Clover Kingdom's magic knights would cower before you!
No! They live?!
No! They've used their own so on!
Now! добр Bibb open by organize!
Aaaaah!
See you.
I feel it You are frozen
I feel it I can't
You are frozen
It will be that you will fight
I feel it
You are frozen
Your dream is frozen
Devonely....
lights.